Tom is here for another day
This one's a little heavy.
Cables to the workshop
Where you wanna go?
lets move it down there
We will use two
Because you can fill up another when i’m dumping
Yeah.
I need to get that square faced shovel
That's the best one, I think. Yeah,
it's a bit flatter.
Yeah.
so a bit more gravel there...
I'll put some butter on it
and toast it in the pan.
Sounds good.
Is the bread dry?
a little bit, yea
the trick is a little sprinkle of water.
and then toast it
it will steam it from the inside.
that's how they do it at the bakery as well.
If they didn't sell
the bread from yesterday.
And the oven has a steamer
Put it in a hot oven with hot steam, and it will revitalize it
nice.
That's ok
That's not.
I can’t put in gravel
with the drainpipe there, no?
I have to wait.
I have to glue these ones up. Okay.
It's a different system.
leftovers from...
From another job? Yeah.
So, yeah, I can go on top of the burrito
the solid pipes will be connected to the rain gutters
3G10/7AWG underground cable
the old trailer is repaired
fertilized eggs from a local chicken breed: Millefiori Piemontese
Enough digging for this week.
Quite a lot of soil has moved
out of the trench and back into it.
Yeah, the drainpipes are all in
that we dug yesterday or last week.
So there’s two pipes on either side.
One for the roof drainage.
So later I'll connect rain gutters.
And the other pipe is a perforated French drain
for ground water
that comes near the cabin.
So they can both separately drain.
I could have connected them half way,
but it's kind of nice to see if I can see them dripping.
Later, they will be connected with the drainage of the second cabin, which will be dug
probably next year.
And then there's also a water pipe going in, for a faucet
and, drainage coming out.
the channels for that were already built in underneath foundation before we poured it.
Two years ago. And,
Yeah, that drain was sitting quite deep.
And because it needs to slope down,
I needed to dig a very deep trench there just in front of the door.
That's all in there
now, as well as electricity cables.
Two, because I need to run the machine simultaneously,
like a dust extractor and a saw.
So they're on two separate groups,
quite thick cables.
10mm2
I think in gauge, that’s 8 eight gauge
They need to be six because otherwise
it could be a voltage drop
because some machines
that will draw 3kW or so.
Yeah.
So that's all in there.
And, yea it was quite a rainy week.
Beautiful today.
a little bit more digging to do.
to fill the trench on the other side.
I think another a load of gravel,
and then we're getting there.
Clean it up,
seed some grass,
put some gravel on the roads,
and then it looks like, neat again.